Who is John Galt?
Atlas Shrugged: Part II is a drama, science fiction,
mystery film directed by John Putch.
Railroad owner Dagny Taggart and steel mogul Henry Rearden search
desperately for the inventor of a revolutionary motor as the U.S.
government continues to spread its control over the national economy.
Dagny Taggart, played by Samantha Mathis.
Henry Rearden, played by Jason Beghe.
Francisco d'Anconia, played by Esai Morales.
James Taggart, played by Patrick Fabian.
Lillian Rearden, played by Kim Rhodes.
Eddie Willers, played by Richard T. Jones.
Atlas Shrugged: Part II (or Atlas Shrugged II: The Strike) is a 2012 American science fiction drama film
serving as the second installment in a trilogy adapting Ayn Rand's 1957 novel Atlas Shrugged.
Although it contintues directly after Atlas Shrugged: Part I
(2011), it features an entirely different cast.
Directed by John Putch, the film stars Samantha Mathis, Jason Beghe,
Esai Morales, Patrick Fabian, Kim Rhodes, Richard T.
Jones, and D.
Atlas Shrugged: Part II was released on October 12, 2012.
The film was largely panned by critics and was a box office bomb, grossing
only $3.3 million worldwide against a $10 million budget.
Despite Part II being a critical and financial failure, the final installment in the trilogy, Part
III: Who Is John Galt?, was released in 2014, also featuring an entirely different cast.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and mind_bending.